ANSIMA CIBALINDA Elvis



■ansimapersic@gmail.com \$\+243 971 774 989

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ansima-cibalinda-elvis-9a658415b/

https://elvisansima.netlify.app, https://app.codesignal.com/profile/ansima_elvis,

SUMMARY

Experienced PHP Web Developer adept in all stages of advanced web development. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

EXPERIENCE

FullStack developer

Evoludata

- Contribute to open source solutions available including (Tiki CMS and WikiSuite) using PHP, Vanilla Javascript, MySQL, Git etc....
- Bug tracking and reporting in the codebase at evoludata.
- Working with the team to develop and follow coding standards and best practices.

FullStack software engineer

CTLCo Sarl

January 2022 - Present. Goma, DRC / Part-time

- Develop a FinTech Application and Deploy API for bank payment integration using top technology stack including CI/CD pipelines, Laravel and VueJS.
- Developed a microservices architecture and scaled the application to support high traffic.
- Wrote automated tests and optimized the code for performance using PHPUnit.
- Worked on the frontend using VueJS and integrated the payment gateway with the backend.

Electronics and IT Engineering Manager

CTLCo Sarl

October 2020 - December 2021. Goma, DRC / Full-time

- We have launched with success an HRM Cloud Application which gains clients and increased overall income of the company (https://demo.vantoria.ctlcosar.com).
- Build Saas Applications & Embedded solutions for Attendance System.
- Work closer with a team of developers for the design, development, and deployment of a cloud-based HRM solution.



Design and Simulation of COMPUTER VISION POWERED ROADS TRAFFIC CONTROL AND CAR SPEED TRACKER

Self • January 2021 - Present

- · Develop A web application capable of monitoring Road traffic and control traffic light accordingly.
- A first prototype has been released and was able to simulate car speed tracking, plate number scanning and smart traffic lights https://github.com/ElvisAns/traffic_management_system/.

School Management System

Self • December 2020 - March 2021

• Build a school management system with attendance tracking features and financial management for administration https://github.com/ElvisAns/school-management-system/.

Smart Health Monitor

Self • December 2019 - Present

- Develop and Implement an IoT system for Healthcare Industry using Electronic Sensor, PHP, Javascript and Data Visualization.
- A first prototype has been released. We measured Blood Pressure, SPO2, Patient Body Temperature and the data got displayed on a remote screen https://github.com/ElvisAns/smarthealthcare.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Electronics and Telecommunications Engineering

Minor in Software Development & IoT • Kigali Independent University • Kigali, Rwanda • 2021 • 4.3

High School diploma in Electronics Engineering,

Minor in Mechanical Engineering • ITIG Goma • Goma, DRC • 2017 • 3.25

CERTIFICATIONS

Responsive Web design

FreeCodeCamp • 2022 https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/ansimaelvis/responsive-web-design

Modern Web Design

Gymnasium • 2022

https://www.credential.net/162d7fba-6223-45aa-8e2d-749c9be5eaf2

PHP FullStack

Development StudySection • 2022

https://www.studysection.com/users/socialMedia/NDc2MDI5/YW5zaW1hcGVyc2ljQGdtYWlsLmNvbQ==

Web Development

IBM • 2019

https://www.credly.com/badges/38808962-d8af-493b-873f-220441b75e9a/public_url

SKILLS

Front-End: HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, Bulma CSS), Javascript (Vanilla, Vue JS & Jquery), ES6

UI/UX: Photoshop, Figma, Canva & Framer

Database: SQL(MySQL, PostgreSQL) & NoSQL(MongoDB)

Backend: PHP (Laravel, Codelgniter) & NodeJS (Express JS). Wordpress Plugin development

Devops: Cloudfoundry, Jira, Buddy, Gitlab, Github

Other: Project & Team Management, Problem thinking & Brainstorming, Innovation, Communication, attention to details, creativity.